⁉ JULy Mayne
Warlord Abyss Ova
Thank you for watching!
Hi everyone, er, I'm so glad that you are watching Sakurazaka Channel, er, I mean, Sakurazaka Channel.
My name is Daisuke Tomiyama. Last July, I was the first guest on the Sakurazaka Channel in commemoration of the release of Sakurazaka46's sixth single, "Start Over," and I was also the first guest on the Sakurazaka Channel to collaborate with the King Masa, which was over half a year ago. This is the 8th release.
I'd like to ask you how old you are, and, uh, since this program is being made to commemorate this release, I'd like to invite you, the members, if you don't mind my speaking by myself.
According to my memory, the last time I asked the three of you to come in, you didn't come in,
I think they are not the people who do the same kind of descent from the stones. I think that they are not the people who would do the same kind of descent.
They should be able to come in soon. Yes, I will.
When I turn to my left, there are three of them, and I am stepping on them.
I'll take one look...three of them. There probably will be.
See.
Says.
a with a selfie stick a Fuji of a Fuji of a Fuji of a
It's like I'm in the selfie, and Hikaru is looking at the camera with a straight face.
I'm good for a jive.
I'm not my mother, hahaha, everyone else only sees the 10-second skip, so I'm pretty sure I'm going to go boom-boom when I'm not in the picture.
Surely there's someone who's stopping them from doing what's right, someone who's masterminding the whole thing, every time.
He came in with a reluctant look on his face. Oh well.
Heavy good morning, thank you.
Well, well, well... but I'm going at a bit too fast a pace... but we'll do it anyway... today.
Well, well, well, well, well, well.
Whoever it is that's making sure they don't get in, there must be three of them.
You heard me, not already. Someone said, "Here you go, three.
Someone says, "Let's not do that, let him be alone." Hmmm...
Then who told you this time?
So that's what it's come to?
etc.
Yes, sir.
a Toemma, this is Toemma.
It's begun, it's begun.
I'm afraid of what you're going to say to me.
I just saw on youtube that before this show, you know, I started my own thing in January, and I've been working on it.
Like a routine, you know, like, a good night's work, or a good night's sleep, or a good night's work, or a good night's sleep, or a good night's sleep, or a good night's sleep.
I don't know how many times it's been played.
What's so funny?
I don't have anything to lose. I have nothing to lose, and that's great.
I've got tentacles that are even more different from yours, and I've got tentacles that are going to go away, I'm telling you.
Tell me that the food is different, and that my sister is on the team of the upstart.
In that video, well, I'm not consciously aware of what I must do that night in that normal life.
But when the camera was rolling, I realized that this is what I was doing.
I'm sure you've all done this or that, even if you don't realize it.
I'm not sure what you're talking about, but I'm sure you're talking about the fact that you've been aging yourself through the camera.
He says "mc" and "something" a lot.
I didn't realize I was saying that, and when I asked him about it later, he said, "I've been saying it a lot.
I tend to say things because of the image I have, but yes, I talk and talk on the spot, so when I think about it, I say it.
I've heard that when you're conscious of something, you can't say it anymore, and you get in trouble again.
Tenchan.
I say, "Laugh at the flowers.
What kind of timing?
Yeah. The last thing I want is to come off as someone who's up to something.
Hey, you know what, I could be the evil equivalent of a bad guy.
You didn't mount him or anything, because I'm trying to soothe him, Airmon.
You say it with the same expression as Buber, so it's cute.
Buber paper
Boober, please watch and see when I take the video!
Buber and Simi Simi are to be avoided as much as possible.
No, that's why I don't pull it off at all. I said it.
I mean, it might even come out, you know, like a mushi or something, so the sound of a live show, it's gonna be there, it's gonna be stable.
That's possible. That's scary.
Karin-chan, I've recently noticed that I look at people very carefully, as the shopkeeper told me.
You didn't notice anything about that, did you?
I don't know... did I already do that?
Yes, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right.
Awesome thank you thank you thank you what a thank you thank you for looking
I'm sure you'll watch it, I've been watching it since the first episode.
I may have mentioned this somewhere else, but we were playing a game where we all flew our slippers.
Onuma-san said that the form of the cat was very beautiful and pure, and that it could fly very well, and when I tried it on the stage, I found that the cat's form was very beautiful and pure.
I love it when the slippers fall off and we all fall over.
Anything so I rewound and watched it several times. a I laughed too.
I hear he's the type that breaks down when he laughs too hard.
I'm making it a place where you can see that.
But it's not only for the baseball team, but also for baseball games, when there is a good scene and everyone can dance.
He's dancing like this, he's dancing like this.
I like to see something that says
I'd like to introduce myself to you because I haven't introduced myself yet, and your name to the camera.
Hello, I'm Yoshikazu Fujiyoshi from Sakurazaka 46.
I'll do my best.
Hello, hello, hello to all Sakurazaka Channel viewers!
I'm Morite Hikaru, nice to meet you.
Yes, at the Yamazaki store.
abbr. of particle "ni" (used especially when it precedes the verb "naru")
So, for the second time today, yes, I'm happy to be here, and I'm happy to be here with all my buddies.
I'm very happy to be able to spend the same amount of time with you through that screen, and I'm very happy that the management is doing this, too.
I'm very happy with the response I've received.
Oh no, this seat!
I'd like to fold up a bit and switch seats. I'd like to take Calicornia.
I didn't make it today.
I liked Boober's death, surely the former was this way, surely I like it though I love it immensely.
I'm sure you're a butt lover, right?
Well, well, well, well... I had an uncle, so I thought I'd give it a try.
I don't know what Hikaru-chan is, but I'm glad I got to see it.
I'm so glad I'm going to watch it over dinner! This is the second time I've seen it today, and the last time I saw Kalincher and Ten-chan.
I had a great time at the first one, too.
Huh.
I went to the radio by item and heard the sound too.
I'm not in the mountains. c I'm listening to something called a "photocaster.
We are playing
And Hikari, last time?
It was fun, I enjoyed it, too.
Good.
It was fun.
Please let me appear on the Higashiyama Channel as soon as possible.
We met in the city by chance once before.
They will come to us at that time.
I'm glad because I came too.
This is Hikaru's first time to do this zagumi,
My previous image,
Ten-chan really speaks as he thinks, doesn't he?
I find that very fun and interesting.
Karin, you're going deep in thought again, with your usual image.
Last time, we had Hono Tamura.
Yes, it is.
Hono-chan.
You can't get it together, Hono.
It's like getting in between, and going left and right.
It was also very interesting.
Hikaru, when it comes to these three people, balance and so on.
No, it's new.
Oh, really?
What kind of place.
I think it is the most interesting.
What? Raise the bar?
Raising the bar so high.
It's hard work.
He is an interesting person.
Where's Hikaru?
I just don't think the world is getting the message very well.
I guess so.
Then you know what Ten-chan and the others know, don't you?
Hikaru-chan's idea of what would be interesting to do this way.
Uh, yes.
Can you pull it out?
So, I'm going to make a good pass in the middle of the day.
Let's go for it.
And Hikaru-chan decides ten.
Yes.
It doesn't feel like that at all.
Isn't that a little scary? What will they draw out of you?
I wouldn't say that.
That's right.
But he said it's like private.
But natural?
Totally natural.
It's just the way it's always been, so if you're there.
It's nice. Today.
Glad to hear it.
OK, then we'll go ahead with it.
In addition!
Um.
Oh, God, I'm sorry. Please go ahead.
Take your headphones off for a second.
I'm listening to another radio.
I'm listening to something else on the radio.
That's weird!
I'm here.
I feel really weird.
What's the laugh now?
Mr. Toyama was interesting.
Where?
No, not applause.
I'm not making any progress.
Oh no, it's only two pages.
It's always like this.
I'm the one who's pissed off about this.
To the management and the staff.
Staff.
There's the scale and all that.
Well.
That's right.
Sakurazaka46, you guys are,
The eighth single.
Yes.
How old do you want to be again?
The fact that this is already on the market.
Yes.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
This is because,
The music video is now available for viewing,
We, too, are said to know the whole story of the song.
Recently, I've been using this method all the time.
Yes, it is.
Wait for premium publication at the same time,
Waiting for the countdown,
I had a chance to look at it.
The three are,
You may have heard this before,
When do you ask first?
I heard about it around the area where they shoot music videos.
That much?
Lyrics.
I see.
Then after hearing the song first,
You mean there's a word for it?
It always is.
Is the image still different?
From the song.
It does not change at all.
It changes, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Hikaru and this time,
How old do you want to be again?
When you heard the song, what kind of things came to your mind?
What is the intro,
It's a little something,
Um,
A fight-based cartoon begins.
Like the sound of a guitar.
Yes.
Lulu Lulu,
Like walking away.
Hang on dakadakadakadakadakadakadakadakadakadakadakadakadak.
Yes.
It's like, is it a tough song or something?
I thought it was going to be a bright tune, but it turned out to be surprisingly cheerful,
It was pretty much like some kind of coming of age.
When I first heard about it,
Come lyrics and all that,
Like, start showing off,
The impression will be totally different,
It's kind of strange, isn't it?
How about you, Karin?
When I first heard about it,
Like the impression of the
Do you remember any of them?
Eh, but it was like Ten-chan the whole time.
Something,
Take everyone in tow.
It's always like that, isn't it?
But who is Ten-chan?
Like a dressing room.
But, no?
Stop calling me Tenchan.
What? What? What?
ten?
Yeah.
Oh, sorry.
Both are good.
What do you mean?
You mean you flirted with him because he was in public?
No, no.
Oh, really?
You're always Ten-chan.
Eh, I see.
You've changed recently, Tenchan.
Eh, I thought. I know, right?
What? Did it change?
See, that's right.
I became a tenchan, recently.
Me.
Oh, why is that?
The other day, I was like, "Oh, Ten-chan, right? And so on.
Ten, well, well, well, ten,
Why are you talking?
Tenchan backstage, too,
I feel like I'm bringing something with me.
Something like that,
Focus on a lively ten,
The feeling of being in a friendly atmosphere,
Even when I heard some kind of tune,
It's like, oh, it's like ten-ish.
Yeah.
Something fast,
Choreography?
I'd love to see them dancing.
That one in the middle.
You sound like you have one word for it.
No, no, no, it's just that that's the image I got when I heard it.
It's fine.
I know, right?
What's one thing you just said?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not true.
But it's very tenchan-like.
I wanted to see Ten-chan's center again in the first place.
Personally, that's why I was so happy when that announcement was made.
And I was happy when they announced it at the center.
She was delighted.
I rejoiced.
I was like, "Oh, my God, that's great!
Something about the three of us again.
We worked together quite a bit at the beginning of Sakurazaka.
Back then, there were even jackets with the three of us on them, like Nobody's Fold.
Something about that time of year.
What?
I had the feeling that the three of us were getting through it together.
I'm looking forward to having that kind of experience again.
certainly
was
When announced
happy
How about you, Tenchan, what did you think when you first heard this song?
something or other
It's very J-Pop-ish, isn't it?
I remember something amazing about Honno saying he loves it so much.
The type that Hono-chan herself likes in terms of feel.
He heard the sound and said he loved it so much.
The music video is already finished, of course.
As Karin mentioned in her story, in those early days, the three of us used to do a lot of work together.
It's like there was a jacket or something.
I thought it was an important scene in the music video though.
I think it's the second rust.
Tenchan and Hikaru face each other and desire to witness
Then Ten-chan and Rin-chan started over.
The last two films there, well...
I think there are a lot of ways to express it, like bumping into each other.
It looked like they were passing it to each other or something.
I don't know, I'm just...
The sixth one, the seventh one, and so on and so forth until now.
or you can give them all of them as well.
I'm willing to throw that out there, too, and ask you to move on.
I saw the scene as if he was entrusting it to Ten-chan.
And it looked like he wanted me to take him further from there.
I thought it was a very important scene.
I think it's wonderful that the three of them are here together like this, Tenchan.
That scene was especially hot.
happy
That's nice, right there in the scene.
Glad to hear it.
I'm so happy!
Isn't that Director Kato?
Director Shujin, the director of the filming of the music video, told me that when he was shooting the music video, he had to
Did you have any detailed instructions?
I was told to be charismatic anyway.
It was extremely difficult.
The charisma that Mr. Shujin imagines is
You know, makeup and all that.
I'm drawing freckles.
I drew freckles and my hair was really long.
That seems to be pretty much in the image.
Something amazing and unexpected came along.
I was like, "Ew!
I answered in my own way by asking you to be charismatic in a big way.
I mean the result of what I saw was that wonderful thing.
What's that laugh you just did?
Are there about three people here today?
I'm scared.
I am.
Of course, Mr. Sakata's 46 as a whole is once again fantastic.
I thought it was a great idea after I finished reading it.
The last one, Tenchan.
It's at the scene outside, one scene before the last one at the bar.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
You'd smile.
That face.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
Like when I joined a much older group.
I saw a very innocent expression on her face.
You know what I mean?
(esp. of men) one's prime (approx. age 30)
something or other
It was so young.
It's not too innocent, is it?
But lately.
Sometimes you can see that side of them.
Performance Time
Wow.
You mean you can feel it during a clive or something?
It could be that difficult.
But I often feel it.
Too many?
I never had one before, but since I finished shooting that music video,
I see it sometimes, that girl.
I am more than when you all joined the group,
Maybe it's the same for everyone,
I've been watching and doing so since the days of Zelkova,
We are also looking at when they first came in.
Isn't this scary? Not this story.
Not at all.
I'm a little surprised now.
I really felt that way at the time.
Everyone now, and Tenchan too,
It's so cool,
I always think I'm seeing something numbing live,
But it didn't happen all of a sudden,
After overcoming it based on many things throughout the years,
Now there's a cool Tenchan.
Even at that former time, the innocent Tenchan is still there,
Of course, I wondered if they were still around.
The person who was then is now doing it, he says.
It's not like I jumped over there and went over there.
I felt that in an instant.
I'm happy too. It is.
You've already got it right now.
He said he agreed.
I was just about to say that's what I'm doing too,
I was surprised that it came out as, hmm? I was just like, "What the heck?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Karin.
I just pushed him away so suddenly.
He said they must have gone to the same place.
Isn't that unusual?
I can only apologize for this.
Interesting.
It means you thought a lot of things.
Excellent. Again.
Thank you very much.
Now, from here, I would like to introduce this one, which was solicited from Buddies.
Let's say, Tenchan.
Hey, listen to me for a second.
I want to see now. Me, my dream.
Volume is bad.
Tired today?
It's fun.
Sakurazaka46's first single to be sold.
In celebration of the release of How Old Do You Want to Go Back?
That's the dream I'd like to see from all of you Buddies right now.
Like the future you want to envision from this point in time.
We are looking for messages from everyone.
Again, we have received a tremendous number.
Thank you very much.
And from those who sent many,
I can't be with all of them, though,
What kind of dreams do you want to see now, by calling them directly?
That's what I'm going to talk about with you all.
They should be on the other end of the phone by now.
Call only.
Can you make it, phone.
It will work.
You just noticed that now?
Ten-chan was running alone and no one was following her.
I'm coming from the day to the middle of the day.
Why did you leave in the middle?
They should be on the other end of the phone by now.
It should be.
Call only.
Only.
Can you make it, phone.
It will work.
I'm not sure where to take it.
It was like Mayumi said in her two-character series on Mayumi's ass.
When I finally said, "Are you going? I was running, so I was left behind.
We didn't even get started, Karin.
Yeah?
No, you didn't. You didn't even close it down.
It was so usual that I didn't go through with it.
Because it's energy efficient.
Then, if you could just say a little Karin-chan hello to the best of your ability,
Maybe the buddies on the other end of the phone will answer.
If this is a half-hearted hello, you probably won't get it.
Feelings, the volume of the voice and all that, but feelings.
Feelings.
I feel like I'm going to connect the phones, and this is probably what I'm going to accomplish.
You can spend as much time as you want, Karin.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Hello.
See, it's not coming out. See?
Worst. Worst.
See, this won't get it out. I'm sure. See?
If Karin is not good enough, then Hikaru or Ten.
Let me do it. Let me do it. No more chances.
Certainly here in the sun-like reputations.
Please.
Can I have one more moment to say hello to Karin-chan? Chance.
Of course.
Keep it together. Properly.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Hello.
Thanks, it's just Buddies. And.
I am Yoshin Fujiyoshi. I am Hikaru Morite. I am Tenchan.
Thank you for your patience.
May I ask you to tell me your buddy's name?
Yes, I'm Tomo. I am Tomo and I am 19 years old from Miyagi Prefecture.
Tomo.
Did you have to wait long?
Tomotomo.
Yes, I did. I was waiting nervously.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you very much.
Are you 19 years old and a student now? Working?
Until recently, I was attending a university for a while, but I quit last November to fulfill my dream.
Oh.
Ehh.
So, that's the theme of this talk, right? But first of all, Tomo-san, if you are nervous now, do you know about Sakurazaka 46?
I love it. Thank you very much. I'm very happy. How did you get started?
I had been listening to their music since the Zelkova era, but my friend was a buddy of theirs,
He sent me the music video of "Start Over" and asked me to watch it because he was sure I would be hooked,
And when I saw it, it was totally different from the image I had imagined of an idol.
I thought it was very cool and cool, so I started to really support it.
Thank you.
I also have my own words that are solid.
I haven't heard that in a while.
Oh, the song? It's playing in my headphones right now.
Thank you so much for your kindness!
there you go, Tomo-san
This time, you are sending me my dream that I want to see now.
Even if you tell me again what kind of dream you want to see now...
May I?
I want to be a major leaguer and play an active role.
Too cool.
It's too good, isn't it?
When did you start having these dreams?
When I started playing baseball, I was interested in Japanese professional baseball.
In the course of playing baseball.
When you look at international athletes and such, they're really all...
He is so good that you wonder if he is really a human being.
The excitement of the crowd over there was really, truly unparalleled.
I wanted to compete head-to-head with great players overseas.
Oh, that's strong.
If I say this is normal, it's normal, but...
Generally speaking, to get to the major leagues...
There's high school, there's college, there's a professional career, and then you go from there.
I think it's the way to be a major leaguer in general.
I know you're out of college, so there's that.
That's right.
Where does this come from?
Get back into an American university.
I joined a baseball team at an American university.
It will be in the form of aiming for the major leagues.
Those things are getting bigger and bigger.
There's a way to do that.
Have you decided to go to an American university?
that's so, isn't it
When?
In September, in case you missed it, the rules for sports club activities at American universities
If you don't get an offer, you can't join the club.
I've just signed a contract with an agent.
Send the video of yourself playing to the college director over there.
I've been approached by five or six schools.
I'm still willing to talk to you and let you decide if you like it.
I haven't decided on a school yet.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
Ten-chan is already an amazing athlete at this point, isn't she?
Are you okay?
I'm sure that means he's probably pretending right now.
I see
of swinging.
by all means
Indeed, it is so
Phone order?
Phone order of course it does
Swing generously at any time of the day.
Yes.
Are you listening to me right now?
Can you hear me now?
I hear you.
Oh, there it is.
Or after the war.
What are you working on now?
Now I go to an English prep school first.
I'm learning English and
We have a motion analysis facility.
Shoot a video of yourself throwing with a high speed camera.
Let me analyze that with my trainer.
And then I check to see what's wrong with it.
Wow! Hikaru, have you heard of this? Like this.
There isn't.
Hey! That's great.
That's great.
Now, Tomo-san, of course you are excited and looking forward to it, right?
But you are still anxious about some things?
Yes, sir.
What are you worried about?
As we dive into the unknown
I was so anxious every day.
Before the members became idols
Thank you for watching!
I think my life has really changed a lot since I became an idol.
So, I am wondering what you do when you feel anxious or crushed by pressure.
I see
I have this.
If I go, if I go to America, I really probably have too much to do.
I'm probably too desperate for what's in front of me, rather than insecure or anything.
I think it's so hard that I can't even think about anxiety and that kind of thing.
Well, I don't get what you're saying, but I'm not saying it's not true, but it really is true, and it really was true.
I don't think it's so much about homesickness or anxiety because of the new environment.
I don't know what it is. There are so many things that have to be done that way.
I think I can be so desperate that I can't even think about it, so I'm probably not ready to jump in right now, and I have a lot of time to think about it.
It's making me more and more anxious, but I guess that's just the way it is, isn't it?
Just jump in and you'll be fine, because you're doing well enough.
I think we go there because we like it, so I think we also go there because we like it.
There are things like love, and there are a lot of hard times, maybe more than you can imagine, but in the end, it's something.
There is definitely a moment when you think, "I'm here now because I like this.
I think that what I do when I make a decision is the right thing to do, so I think that trusting myself is the best thing to do.
Yeah, how about you, Karin, in response to Tomo-san's story?
Yeah, I guess so.
Talk about incredibly serious.
No, I'm definitely anxious already, because...
I'm going to be living in a different place from where I was born and raised, and I'm going to have a big dream.
What's more, what is the
I'm sure you'll work even harder, my friend.
But good luck, not so much in that life.
I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it.
It's not that it's something that can't be experienced, but rather that it's something that doesn't seem to happen very often, and that's why I was able to encounter this feeling in the first place.
What a great thing to do!
Something I'll be glad to think about later.
There will come a day when we can be thankful for this hard-working, passionate moment.
Someday, when my mind is at peace.
Even Kani-chan, when she first joined a group or performed in a live concert for the first time...
There were times when I was standing in the center for the first time and so on.
certainly
But I tend to listen to music when I need to calm down.
I kind of wish Ton-san would listen to it. A lot. A lot of music.
- What kind of music do you listen to, for example?
- I? On days when I want to be calm, on days when my mind is spiky,
Spitz, for example. I'll listen to them.
Like when I'm being a jerk.
I said to myself, "I have to face myself and my mentality in this way.
I'm going to do it or put it back on the plane first, my friend.
I'm sure you've heard the words from Ten-chan, Hikaru-chan, and Hanawa-chan, but what do you have in mind right now, Tomo-san?
Oh, no. Books.
Yes... I knew it.
I'm really nervous to the point of a heart attack right now, so I'm not sure what to say.
And also!
You scared the hell out of me.
yeah
I think the three of you are right and
cute
I'm really glad I was able to consult with you.
I'm glad you're happy. I'm glad you're happy.
If you're nervous right now because you're talking to people you love and they're saying something to you, and you're nervous right now because you're nervous, maybe you're as nervous as Max is right now in your life, then you're going to be very happy.
Like the pressure of the future.
As a pitcher, that's a hell of a thing to say, especially in the bottom of the ninth inning with two outs when you're absolutely out of position.
Even if they drive you into a corner with 3 balls and 2 strikes or something.
I'm thinking that it might be less nerve-wracking than here. I might be able to make it.
But I hope you enjoy it. The best thing is to have fun.
Tomo-san. Yes, I am.
Well, it's almost time to say goodbye. It's early.
If you have anything you would like to say to the three of us or to Sakurazaka 46, please let me know.
Okay, then. Go ahead.
First of all, congratulations on the new single song.
Thank you very much.
I am waiting for you over there, believing that one day you will perform in the U.S..
I will definitely fulfill my dream and become a major leaguer, so I would be very happy to meet you then.
Good luck. I'll do my best.
They will go to America. I'm sure he will.
I'm going, I'm going. Private.
I'll be there. Absolutely.
Please contact us.
Where?
WHEREAS.
I'm going to pitch at this stadium.
Thank you, Tomo, for your nervousness.
Thank you very much.
Enjoy.
Good luck. I'm rooting for you.
Amazing.
Because even this could really happen, say, four or five years from now.
It's totally possible.
He said, "We were both there at that time.
I want to be. I want to be.
Tomo is throwing.
It's amazing.
I've received so many, so many, so many. This dream of yours.
16 years old female. Buddies name Arthur.
Dear Sakurazaka46 members. Hello Toyama-san.
Hello.
I am a first year high school student living in Kansai.
I am currently a fan of Sakurazaka 46, I am in a band with my buddies girls.
My dream is to someday stand at the same festival as Sakurazaka46.
I will do my best until I see you at the festival.
Cool.
Nice.
It's nice.
Best for.
Support.
I want to hear it.
Or even Sakurazaka songs with the band.
I want to do it.
It's absolutely great.
It's nice.
What do you want to hear? The sound of a band.
Our own songs.
What would you like, Mr. Toyama?
Me?
LLC Plus
Is Curve a comedian, then?
What kind of question is that?
Enough. I'm doing radio.
You don't even know I'm an Auror.
Do you really put in the room that there are a number of ordinary people who like to be ah so ah buddies.
I don't think we're going to have that at Buddy's, Mr. O'Reenie, so you asked me what I wanted to hear from that band.
Why do you like the voice?
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Is this what you guys are like?
I'd like to hear your voice, though the more I say it, the less it sounds like that.
We'll be waiting for you. Sound Source
Boober, cold.
18-year-old female buddy's name Fujiyoshi Children, right? Good evening, Lun, Kari, Teng, and Yama!
My dream is to reduce my foot size.
I'm too shy to say my size when it comes to foot size! No, I'm cute, but nothing special.
It is my dream to be 23.5 cm please support my dream no wait
I'd like to get the one that doesn't sell out of the current size and the sound that 23 centers sell out of.
I think I'm going to have to stop buying shoes and stop changing them. 25.5 26My size, but it's really nice.
Even if you sell all the shoes you want without selling out, you really don't have three more items to sell, you know, they're too small for a man and too big for a woman.
This exquisite size
Well, you've got a really nice size, so I guess I should be proud of you.
25.5 and then again at the end of the phone, so...
So, since Karin-chan has offered to do the "hello, hello" thing, I'll go with either one or both of you. I'm going to do it because I really want to connect and talk with you.
I want you to focus on the "yes" and send it to the screen, or maybe to the microphone.
If it looks like it's going to disappear soon, then I'll just turn the timing around and put up a good fight, because sometimes it doesn't come out.
I don't know how it could have happened, but the colored girl who was just here was very loud at the first shot, and I know when it happens.
Who is it?
Butapana minus, please be careful, it's no good, because it makes it harder to get out, and I'll have to piggyback on it.
I'm going to go in.
Boo Boo, what's wrong with you, you were so cool earlier, are you ready or not?
I'm laughing, aren't I? Okay, I'll go now.
abbr. of particle "ni" (used especially when it precedes the verb "naru")
Quit? I'm quitting, I'm quitting, I'm quitting!
Sorry! You're the one waiting on the other end of the phone!
Coming?
You can even give up!
You are going!
Hello!
This is good!
Oh! There it is! That's good!
Hi, just a buddy's! And.
I'm Yoshin Fujiyoshi.
I am Hikaru Morita.
Just buddies.
But when I asked him if there was, he said yes.
May I ask you to tell me your buddy's name?
I'm Fuka, a 20 year old from Aichi, Japan.
Fuka!
Did you hear Hikaru's Hello?
I heard you!
How did it go?
It was cute!
Thank you.
First of all, you are 20 years old now, right?
Takai Second year.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work, really.
And what about Sakurazaka 46?
A coincidental answer to that coincidental look...
It's not that funny. It's not that funny.
You're laughing too hard, and I'm not going to give you a coincidental answer.
Now, you may not understand.
It's the same as Hayashiya Perko.
From the timing and tone of the moment.
You know what I mean?
Pink.
That laugh at the pun is already
Is there a second generation? Do you think...
I think I'll follow you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Fuuka.
Coincidental answers.
Look at it by chance.
Sorry, coincidence, it happens.
Timing-wise, yes.
You're going for it, I'm sure of it.
And look.
Look at it, and from there, performance and so on.
Attracted by the expressions on their faces.
I'll be rooting for you all the way.
Even from my center, Kalin.
Glad to hear it.
At such a time.
What about live performances? Have you ever been to one?
I've been there a few times.
So, Mr. Kinoshita's Yui Kobayashi's
I went on the second day of the Kotskong.
Thank you.
It was so amazing, wasn't it, Mr. Fuuka?
It was amazing, really.
beautiful
I haven't heard any feedback, come to think of it.
Indeed.
Is it from Ta-da-buddy's?
free buddy
No, but, well, what did Fuka think?
Yes, I did say that once.
What did you think was great about it?
I have always been a fan of Yui Kobayashi.
I was able to continue to see the last of Yui.
I was happy.
Wow, what an amazing live show that brings out the awesomeness of Sakurazaka!
The performances and stuff were amazing.
The start over is particularly
It was cool, like a music video.
Thank you.
Fireworks are going off in the middle like this.
Yes, that's what was so cool about it.
Hugging each other over and over.
Good for you.
You don't forget.
I won't forget it.
I'll never forget it.
That moment that I still remember after all these years.
Yes, thank you.
And then there's Fuka.
Of course you have a dream that you want to see now, don't you?
Yes, sir.
May I ask you about that?
Yes, my dream.
I want to connect the phone with my 6 year old sister who loves Ken-chan.
rough
Let's say you're in the vicinity now.
I'm in the neighborhood.
Should I not ask your sister's name?
It's okay. Your name, yes.
What's up?
It's peach blossom.
Momoka.
Momoka-chan, do you know that there are Sakurazaka members on the other end of this phone today?
I know.
How are you feeling now? How is Momoka?
I'm kind of grinning right now.
cute
Momoka likes Ken-chan.
Yes, I like them all, but I especially like Ken-chan.
You're a good judge of character.
Six years old.
Do you understand? Momoka...
You know what I mean.
What are you going to do, Ken-chan? Momoka is waiting for you.
I miss you, I miss you, come on, come on, come on.
So you're gonna talk now? You're gonna have to change the phone.
I want to talk.
Okay? Fuuka, if you do that...
Yes, I'll change then.
You're a good sister.
It's peach blossom.
Ears healed.
say again
Hello, Momoka!
cute
happiest day of all
I'm sure Tenchan will be fine.
In a voice for Momoka
cute
sob, sob, sob
Momoka.
cute
Tenchan.
son of a god
Yeah, what?
I like to dance.
Like to dance?
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
Momoka-chan, you're so cute. Sorry.
Curry and good together.
Oh, Kachan, I'm sorry, it's just a birdie, Cuin.
Has Momoka-chan ever met Dentenja? No, she hasn't.
Manager likes dancing and where after
Song.
cute
I'm so happy.
I'll sing and dance a lot.
Momoka, is there anything you want to tell Ten-chan?
Too cute.
It was kinky and bizarre.
3 لكن I want to stay °
The number of corporate bodies that have been able to perform απ-ON and furthermore intelligent indicate
It is a matter of local
the number of postconditions has increased
inquiring beforehand
Если Suga
If you like the flavor and color of significant men and women.
I am nine days old
stories (esp. war stories) or lectures told by someone near a Buddhist temple or shrine
Nice color.
cute
I love you.
Do you have a song? Sakurazaka.
start over
That's pretty tight.
certainly
For a six year old.
Momoko-chan...
Karin is here today, too.
fried daikon flavored with salt or soy sauce and thickened with potato starch
You know?
center
He's the one doing the start over.
I love Karin!
cute
Thank you.
happy
daughter of a person of high rank (i.e. a king, noble, aristocrat, etc.)
Yes, sir.
There's another guy from Sakurazaka, too!
Runchan.
You know?
I love Run-chan!
cute
what's that?
You must be too cute.
daughter of a person of high rank (i.e. a king, noble, aristocrat, etc.)
Yes, sir.
It's about time.
I think it's time for me to get some sleep.
certainly
I'm sorry to say goodbye.
Finally.
To Tenchan, Karin, and Runechan.
If there's anything you want to tell me again...
Anything.
Win a live raffle!
live auction
lot
I'd like you to win tickets to the show.
praise extravagantly
I'll give it to you.
Depends on you.
Give me your address and I'll send it to you.
throw in a suggestion
I'll send it to you.
They'll invite you.
Invitation.
Come backstage.
invitation to a meeting place for assignations, drinking, etc.
welcome!
Cute.
Momoka's.
What is your dream for the future?
Idol.
I know.
be grieved
Then doesn't that mean we could be in the same group?
Sakurazaka Come.
obedient
how many times?
cute
Because now, Momoko, you're six years old.
Oh, well.
How long, 8 years, 9 years, 10 years, maybe?
Then we'd have to have three of them.
Really.
What is it?
Can you break dance then?
I can go on, I can go on, I can go on, I can go on.
As long as they get some training in.
Momoko is waiting for you.
Yes.
Thank you, Momoko.
Thank you.
until late
Then to your sister.
See you later, Momoko.
I'll talk to you later.
Put your sister on the phone for me.
Yes, sir.
form of address for young adult female
How did you like seeing this famous 6 year old sister and her desire to connect him to the phone?
I'm glad it came true.
Isn't she too good a sister?
Sure thing, sis.
If you have something you want to tell me, sister, the last thing I want to do is tell you.
wanting to hear
Really thanks to everyone at Sakurazaka.
I'm doing my best every day and will continue to do so for years to come.
My two sisters and I are rooting for you.
Thank you.
It was fun.
I enjoyed it too.
We'd love to talk to you!
(sentence end) indicates emphasis, agreement, request for confirmation, etc.
Thank you very much.
see you later
bye-bye
I'm a little out of breath already, aren't I, folks?
Isn't it wonderful? But even this six-year-old
Like that coolness.
That's what I'm telling you.
that's so, isn't it
So, with Momoko.
I wanted them to sing the song and dance.
I think everyone probably thinks that, so...
Please wait for her, Momoko's.
Yes, sir.
Waiting?
Really wait.
I wonder how many terms they'll get in.
certainly
Even if you can get in at about 5.
Put it in?
I don't know.
That's great.
good time
Healed.
Thank you.
Good for you. Applause.
I haven't been able to read any of your e-mails.
Let's read it.
May I read some of them?
Yes, of course.
please
54 years old male
buddy's name
Mr. Volumetric Daibats
grunting
everyone
How do you do?
I bought a camper and
Wow, I like it.
My dream is to wander around Japan for a month or so without deciding where to go!
Uh, I understand.
Please buy me a camper!
I see.
Buy it!
Yes, sir.
Buy.
So you want everyone to buy it.
54 years old.
You are older.
Yes, 54 years old
Shall I ask him to buy that for me?
Do you have any idea how much it costs?
No, I don't know.
How much is it?
It's pretty expensive.
How much do you think?
Can you get to 100?
It's a car that goes 100 miles.
Like buying a car after all.
It's high, about 10 million.
Ah, but I think that's exactly about it.
I think that's about it. The market is.
He's a good guy.
How do you know so much? I don't.
I just saw something, a video.
It's been happening lately, hasn't it?
Yes, I kind of like watching camping videos.
So you saw something.
I was just wondering how much it would cost.
But even inside, there's, you know, a kitchen.
You can use the restroom and take a shower.
You can make a living, right there.
Some beds and stuff.
Any requests to buy?
yeah
Let's think about it.
Will you think about it?
They'll think about it.
Just think about it.
Just thinking?
Tenchan might be able to get some out of it or something.
This 13 year old female, whose ladys name is
Kohalung acid
Koha Lun
I want to dream of being surrounded by 100 or so Kalin-chan and dancing with them!
Wait, wait, wait. What do you mean?
I want to dream of being surrounded by 100 or so Kalin girls and dancing with them.
Is that a dream over here?
Oh, a sleeping dream?
Dream, I say, dream.
dream
Ah, a sleeping dream.
Please keep up the good work with the support of Sakurazaka.
Thank you.
It has to be 100 people.
even
Yes, it is.
So 100 people surround Mr. Koharun.
scary!
If you're surrounded by me, it's a little...
Try grazing one of them, and you'll be grazed by a hundred.
Oh, then that sounds amazing.
Bad dreams, nightmares?
Maybe I'll see it when I get a big fever.
This dream?
yeah
Will they all be the same Kalin, I wonder if this is the same Kalin.
Maybe they're making a different move or something.
Different visuals or something? The way they're dressed?
Kalin in the front, like this haircut.
Then do that one.
Print out 100 copies of your favorite Jiaylin photos.
It's dark and scary, scary.
Just pull it and go to bed.
That's what you're trying to do, to get them to come to you in your dreams.
It's okay, right?
Please don't.
But a 13-year-old girl?
Thirteen years old?
Thirteen.
Elementary school student?
If this were a 54 year old male volume laughing out loud.
certainly
If it was like a dream where you're sleeping in a camper and you're surrounded by 100 people.
That's scary.
Koharu, a 13-year-old girl.
Pure Dreams
Feelings, man. You're so cute.
You know, the kind of thing where you like it so much that you've turned into 100 people because of it.
I guess this is the last one then.
18-year-old female buddy's radio name
You must be Sen-chan.
My dream is to raise my hands and scream as hard as I can on a roller coaster!
I've been a scaredy-cat since I was a little kid, in elementary school.
I was so scared that I blacked out on a roller coaster ride at Universal Studios Japan.
Since then, I can't ride a roller coaster without gritting my teeth and looking down.
But I love roller coasters.
I want to ride the roller coaster with my hand up!
Like is like.
You mean you're scared, but you like it?
Is she a dominatrix?
Are you a dominatrix?
Maybe he has that temperament.
It's possible.
But I guess that's because fear and laughter are like two sides of the same coin.
How about a roller coaster?
Is there a show or something?
dislike
Kani no?
I really hate it.
Don't even think of riding private?
I absolutely hate it.
I know you've been waiting for me too... alone.
In fact, I went to Universal Studios Japan and was told I could ride the ride.
I waited downstairs by myself while everyone cried.
Don't you want a ride like that?
I don't want to ride.
Scary?
I loved roller coasters.
I rode a really scary one when I was in elementary school.
With a name like White Cyclone.
I got on it and was really scared and couldn't ride anything from there.
Too scary.
But as I grew up, I had a stronger sense of parallelism and walk periods.
Indeed.
Or some people are okay as adults.
Let's take a ride.
Shall we go, Rin-chan?
See you at Sakurazaka Channel.
Would you like to go with me?
It would be funny if I went.
Why?
It would be funny if just a buddy went there.
Back.
noise
I wish I could see this place.
Nice video.
wee
Uh-oh.
by chance
I'm playing with a loose end.
Uh-oh.
Mr. Toyama, if it's a curve, you'll be late.
Comes through late.
On the curve, you just can't see it.
I can just see it.
A different kind of terror awaits.
All the buddies shouted "Enough!
So, the fear of "I'm not going to be able to do it" is an additional burden.
I'm fine.
Are you tired, Mr. Toyama?
I'm not tired.
I ain't tired.
Negative today.
certainly
Who is it?
Yes, it is.
Me?
There's something different about it.
What?
There was something.
Why? Lies?
I consulted with him about his problems.
I'm listening.
I don't need advice about my problems.
Just listen to me for a second.
Mr. Toyama's
No, no, no.
I'm not that normal, not at all.
Did you feel like this?
I wonder what's troubling you.
I'm sure you've had your share of worries.
We all have them, don't we?
Hey? trouble
It's not easy, living.
serious conversation
And it's a lot of work.
serious
Now, we've brought you this release commemorative delivery, and it's time to say goodbye until we see you again!
You're early. What kind of face is that?
I'm so glad you're all standing up so quickly, because we've already decided on a tour title for this tour starting in March, and I'm sure you'll all be excited about it.
I'll let you all present the four numbers.
First of all, well, in case you're wondering, Sakurazaka 4 t 4 tough.
I want to use it as a title, so surely Nakasakuraga is live! Sarazaka 464s Arena Tour
2024 New Cherry Blossom Front 5 sound back
A little cushion space! Great memory!
It's good to know that you have the strongest feelings about the cross-tour. I didn't say a single thing at all, so Ten-chan has already admitted it.
Nod your head. You're not supposed to nod.
March 2 a Marine Messe Fukuoka Kawakiri Yes Fukuoka 2 Days Osaka Castle Hall 2 Days Japan Company Hall 2 Days
Pearina, mm, two deuces, and getting bigger again.
And the scale of the project. Yes, it's a big deal. I'm looking forward to it. I'm sure you are, too.
We've got more songs now, too, and we've got a new unit song, too.
I'm looking forward to the same song, but the production is still totally different from tour to tour.
You know, different stages, different lighting, more impressions, that kind of thing, that's the great part.
I'm embarrassed to admit that this isn't the first time I've seen a camera.
I'm really looking forward to it, and I've never been disappointed because I went on that last tour.
I'm sure you're probably all buddies, but I'm very much looking forward to entertaining you there, too.
I'll be waiting for you... well, most recently, Yui Kobayashi's graduation concert was held at the Yoyogi First Wallet Hall for two days, and I saw the second day of the concert live, and the first day was archived.
I've seen the delivery, and it was great!
How was it, Lynn? Good.
Kobayashi-san... we talked about this on mc, too.
It's so strange... dancing together...
It's different from fun. It's a strange feeling.
That's what I liked, dancing with Mr. Kobayashi. Hmmm, that's still the start over, because there's a lot of interplay between the two of them.
Taste it. Finally.
It was a strange feeling.
It was a beautiful time to be there, and I loved it. I was there thinking, "I can't watch this on a screen.
I just thought I should get a good look at it.
The manager was in tears, too.
It was tough.
Yes, it was sad, and yes, I've already graduated.
I have never really been able to get a sense of what it was like for anyone else.
But lately I haven't really had a chance to meet many of the graduates since I thought there are so many people I haven't met since they graduated.
I think. I'm really feeling it.
I'm really sad to see the number of Exei-san decrease any further.
It was like that.
But, you know, I think Yui was really thinking of us when she stayed here, and I'm sure that's what she was thinking of.
Hey, again, they're letting us know that you're graduating.
I am very happy to think that you think you can do without me from now on, and it makes me think that I have to do my best.
Hikari-chan Yes, that's true, but I don't know.
It was totally different from a live performance, not only in the way I felt, but also in the atmosphere of the fans.
I felt strange because I had experienced so much in two days, and I also felt sad, I don't know why, but I felt sad,
I was carrying something different from my usual live performance, so I felt heavy all the time. Wow.
I wonder if it's all the time.
Like, "What am I going to do? I felt like I was in a hurry. I realized it after it was over. But even after you graduated, I didn't feel like you were really gone yet. I didn't really feel it.
Yes, I was. I was really sad, but Yui was smiling and having fun the whole time. I was having fun.
We were very happy to hear that. We are very happy. It was a wonderful two days.
I saw that Genshi Yonezu also had a bit of a deep feeling when he talked about his family during the last MC session,
But other than that, he was basically smiling all the time, and I think that was a big help to me,
I felt that they must have felt refreshed, saying, "I've done it, I've handed it over, and now it's time to take care of the rest.
Yes, it is.
Each member of the group has various thoughts and feelings, and they travel around the country with them,
I am sure that the new single will be performed again in various places, and I wonder how old they want to go back to.
As a song about buddies, it is a song about looking to the future and how old we want to be again,
For example, 10 or 20 years from now.
When I think about how old I would like to be again, if I could think back to the period when this current single was released, it would be such a wonderful thing. I just wish that every day could be like that.
I think I saw some air leaking out.
He says it's fine.
I guess I said okay. I heard that air leaked out.
I was soaked.
I have to.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ah!
We've already gone over our time limit, and it's very difficult to edit the video.
I know, right?
That edit, but I won't make it.
Yeah, I mean, you only see people who have free time, and they're like, "I'm just going to work," and they're like, "I'm just going to work," and they're like, "I'm just going to work.
Oh, well, I'll take care of that, and I'll take care of it personally. Work Radio Talk
So, let's call more listeners. I'd like to talk to how many people because I've only been able to get two people to call today.
10/22/13 This will be a 6 hour delivery.
If you can still make it, let's do it sometime in that spare time. I'm busy right now, so yeah.
I'd like to do it when I graduate from that high school.
After April, when the students are done with their tours, they'll have to leave for the summer, and the summer will be tough, so...
I'm going to be on live stream for however long we decide on.
I'm going to set the maximum time that we can extend the maximum time that we can't go any further. Okay, so let's take a day off, and let's make that schedule 24 hours.
If you open everyone up for four hours at the maximum, you're definitely only open for one day. One day only.
Yes, you can buy the last one when you want to go home.
If the manager leaves first, there will be a battle of the backsides, with Karin having to stay behind because she's the only one left.
Who'll see Mr. Higashiyama today? I'll be alone until the end.
Cat Lumber Good Time Special and Jump!
I wouldn't do it if I could just lie on my side and write about my ass and then broadcast that live, too.
I'd like to do that sometime in the next 24 hours or so, when I don't have you guys on, and I might want to do a live stream.
I know that 46 hours was a long time ago, and the members changed colors, but you know what they say... when the time is set, the time is set.
I'm sure you've got hours to go, right? That's why I prefer the method of increasing the number of hours.
And if I get in, I'm still going, and that's for a maximum of 24 hours.
Then next time, 24 hours, max delivery.
I'm sure it will be on youtube.
I'm just a buddy, and my partners are Yoshikazu Fujiyoshi, Hikaru Morita, and Tento Yamazaki from Sakurazaka 46, right?
trafficking (e.g. of humans, arms, drugs)
good-bye